We're gonna roll this beautiful hair today.
She has curly hair but it tense to frizz a lot.
So a great way to control frizz is to do a great roller set, a good roller set.
But it really is essential to learn to roll a set properly when you are dealing with curly hair, wavy hair, or frizzy hair.
So we're going to go ahead and look at the hair and see which kind of rollers we want to use.
Also, ask the customer what kind of wave she wants her hair to flow.
Maybe she wants a straighter look.
When I roll it, so I'll use big rollers.
Somewhat like this.
Or maybe the customer wants a more tighter curl.
Wavy like Hollywood now in days and she might want something like this or this.
There's many different types of rollers you know.
I use the smooth type so it doesn't tangle in the hair and it doesn't cause any damage, okay.
Because if it tangles in it you can't get a smooth look.